[{"answer": "Well, I'm not sort of privy to it, but the producers who have been involved with it are mainly people who come from rock.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "How have they got themselves, do you think, into that position?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not a critic, and I never talk about other people's work.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "From a musical perspective, how did you rate it?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Is the narrative key, do you think, to longevity on these things?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Yes, I think -- although \"Evita\" been a very big hit in London -- \"Evita\" when it opened it here, had pretty bad reviews.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Have you had a situation like they've got where it opens and the criticism's pretty heavy, everyone's saying this isn't going to survive, and then it's gone on to be a huge hit?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I don't really care very much if I don't think that the critics really understand music.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "How much have the critics got to you over the years?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Well, I guess if it's somebody who I did respect as a musician said that the score was humdrum or something, then I would be sad if I believed in the score.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "But if it's someone, though, that you respect, what is the most hurtful kind of thing they could say that would really get to you?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, I think the television -- and I've been involved with the television casting programs in Britain.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What do you think it is?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Yes, of course they can.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Can they produce genuine, bona fide stars, do you think?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Susan Boyle -- of course, we all know, it was an extraordinary moment, not just in television, but one of the most extraordinary things that ever happened to a musical, because talk about something out of the blue for \"Les Miserables.\"", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "When you watch a Susan Boyle, for example, what do you think of someone like her?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "You're not doing that anymore, are you?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "I know it's -- it's extraordinary.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, \"The Phantom of the Opera,\" I'm a melodist, but I'm also a theater animal.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "But how does a melody for something like \"Phantom\" come to you?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, I -- to finish the story, Jim Sharman said, no.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Where does this music come from?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Well, \"The Phantom,\" I mean, originally started off, I mean for -- the phrase, I mean the -", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "How do you come up with each song?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Clearly, you can see it does, but I think that's just a very, very one-off example.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "So, it doesn't really matter then, does it?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Sometimes it'll come like that.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "When you say it just comes, I mean, can you literally get almost the whole thing in your head like that?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Ooh.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Which of all your -- I know it's a bit like asking you for your favorite child, but which of all the musicals is your personal favorite, of yours?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Is it true Michael Jackson wanted to play the Phantom?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes, yes I did.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "And did you speak to him about it, seriously?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Well, I think he would.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "He would've been incredible, wouldn't he?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "He wanted to play the Phantom.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Wanted to play the Phantom?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "It's difficult, really.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "If you could relive one moment live again that you've experienced, of all these shows, all the opening nights and everything, which one sticks most in your memory?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I did think that that's fairly extraordinary.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What were you thinking?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Do women find, do you think, musical genius sexy?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Anyone that can just conjure up these kinds of melodies, which then become anthems all around the world, that's genius, isn't it?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "I think some of McCartney's melodies are just sublime.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Well, I've been doing these TV casting series back in Britain.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "How do you work out what you think will catch on for a morning audience?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "It's been good fun.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "That's very exciting, isn't it?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know, because we're in constant touch at the moment.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Is it one of those situations?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, I'm told that Ricky Martin is playing Che.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Any idea who may be starring in this?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "I'm beginning to think that it's off to the village I live in called Daer (ph), and early retirement.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Are they cutting out the problem, do you think, here?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "You don't have a mobile phone, cell phone?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "I can't remember now exactly.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Saying what?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Well, it doesn't work.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Can you use the iPad?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Could it be you that's the problem and not the iPad?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "This has to do with the iPad.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Was this actually you?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Elvis.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "If you were casting the all time dream musical, who would you want standing on that stage?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Most surreal.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What's been the most surreal, kind of pinch me moment you've experienced, do you think, for you personally?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "You played and he sang?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I was actually feeling, please do not mess up.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What were you actually feeling when you came out?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "I just turned 11.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Because you don't have the voice of a normal -- how old are you now?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "I believe that it comes from God.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Where do you think this voice comes from?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "You know, to say that she is at the top of the heap would be an understatement.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "How does Jackie rank, given her age, do you think?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Yeah, I do.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "You find all this quite funny, don't you?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "My life is kind of a back and forth thing.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "What's your life like?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "The truth of the matter is she could go either direction in terms of pop or opera, because she has a great understanding of both, not unlike Andrea Bocelli.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "How far could Jackie go, do you think?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "I get a lot more nervous -- I do get nervous.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Do you ever get nervous now or not?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "These are going to be tracks from your new album, is that right?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "I'm going to be singing a song called \"Angel\".", "docId": "110701pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "Jackie, what are you going to sing for me?", "qSentId": 723}]